gammerson.com 2017-06-13

# Privacy Policy-Gammerson

### _**Privacy Policy for www.gammerson.com**_

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contactus by email at himalayasaxena@gmail.com.At ****www.gammerson.com**** , the privacy of our visitors is of  
extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines  
the types of personal information is received and collected by **www.gammerson.com** ****and how it is used.

__**Log Files**__

Like many other Web sites, **www.gammerson.com** makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (  
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze  
trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and  
gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information  
are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

__**Cookies and Web Beacons**__

****www.gammerson.com**** does use cookies to store information about  
visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages  
the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors  
browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their  
browser.

__**DoubleClick DART Cookie**__

1\. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on   www.gammerson.com.

2.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.gammerson.com and other sites on the Internet.

3\. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.gammerson.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the  
advertising content that you see. www.gammerson.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.gammerson.com ’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie  
management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’  
respective websites.

**We use cookies to personalise  
content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our  
traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our  
social media, advertising and analytics partners.**
